Yun-Yun Tsai

alice10300004@gmail.com (+886)973-798-908 https://yunyuntsai.github.io/

RESEARCH INTERESTS

I'm a master student and research assistant in National Tsing Hua University. My research focuses on Artificial Intelligence Security, adversarial machine learning toward the robustness of deep neural networks, including attack, defense and robust evaluation. I'm currently working with Dr. Tsung-Yi Ho and Dr. Pin-Yu Chen from IBM research.

EDUCATION

National Tsing Hua University

Hsinchu, Taiwan

M.S. in Computer Science

Sep. 2018 - Jun. 2020

Advisor: Dr. Tsung-Yi Ho

Overall GPA: 4.18 / 4.3

National Tsing Hua University

Hsinchu, Taiwan

B.S. in Computer Science

Sep. 2014 – Jun. 2018

Overall GPA: 3.5 / 4.3 Last 60 GPA: 3.89 / 4.3

PUBLICATIONS

- Yun-Yun Tsai, Pin-Yu Chen, Tsung-Yi Ho, "Transfer Learning without Knowing, Reprogramming black box machine learning model with scarce data and limited resources," in Proceeding of International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML), 2020.
- Yun-Yun Tsai, Pin-Yu Chen, Tsung-Yi Ho, "Adversarial Machine Learning for Social Good: Reprogramming black box machine learning model with scarce data and limited resources," Advances in Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) NewInML Workshop, Poster, 2019.
- Honggang Yu, Kaichen Yang, Teng Zhang, Yun-Yun Tsai, Tsung-Yi Ho, Yier Jin, "CloudLeak: Large-Scale Deep Learning Models Stealing Through Adversarial Examples," in Proceeding of Network and Distributed System Security Symposium (NDSS), 2020.
- Ta-Wei Huang, **Yun-Yun Tsai**, Chung-Wei Lin, Tsung-Yi Ho, "Vehicle Sequence Reordering with Cooperative Adaptive Cruise Control," In Proceeding of Design, Automation & Test in Europe Conference & Exhibition (DATE), 2019.

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Graduate Research Assistant

July. 2020 – present

Advisor: Dr. Tsung-Yi Ho

THETA Lab, NTHU, Hsinchu

Focus on the research about federated learning system and sophisticated adversarial attack.

Visiting Scholar

Mar. 2019 – Aug. 2019

Advisor: Dr. Yier Jin

HSL at University of Florida (UF), Gainesville, Florida

Focus on model retrieving attack on large-scale Deep Learning Model.

Software Engineer Intern

Jul. 2017 – Jun. 2018

Microsoft Azure IoT Team Taipei, Taiwan

- Built POC (covers Smart City/Retail/Home/Manufacturing) leveraging Azure IoT Cloud services to demonstrate IoT solutions to 10+ technical business partners.

Microsoft 2017 Coding Angel, R&D Leader

 Designed/Created Azure Machine Learning hands-on materials with Microsoft MVPs and delivered the workshop in coding angel event to 100+ college STEM female students.

PROFESSTIONAL Skills AND ACTIVITIES

Invited talk at CYBERSEC - Aug. 20. 2020

 Giving a keynote about "CloudLeak: DNN Model Extractions from Commercial MLaaS Platforms" at CYBERSEC Taiwan 2020, one of the largest cybersecurity conference and exhibition in the Asia Pacific Region.

Programming Languages

- C/C++, Python, Verilog, etc.
- Package: Deep Learning Framework (ex: Tensorflow, Pytorch), Scikit-Learn, Keras, etc.

Certification

Microsoft Professional Program Certificate in Data Science

ACTIVITIES

Music

- Play the piano and viola over 15+ years and have lots of performing experiences.
- 1st prize of viola solo and piano quintet in The National High School Student's Music Contest Finals in Taiwan.

First stand of Viola, National Tsing Hua University Orchestra, 2014-2018

- Perform orchestral works for audiences ranging from 50-10,000 people.
- Perform Symphony No.7 by Beethoven at Taiwan National Concert Hall, 2016.

Piano concerto soloist, Annual summer concert of NTHU orchestra, May.30 2017

 Won the concerto competition in National Tsing Hua University and played Piano concerto No.2 in C minor by Rachmaninoff with NTHU orchestra.

Director of Team Mentors, Dept. of CS, NTHU, 2016

- Led 20 mentors (college students) to train 100 participated senior high school students on basic computer science.

Student Association committee, Dept. of CS, NTHU, 2016-2017